Jhal Hello friends, Namaskar, welcome to all of you once
again in my today's
video. In today's video, we will
tell you that if you have sent your bike
and someone else has taken that bike, then
after the bank transfer, does the
insurance get transferred? Yes friends, the
answer is yes, if you have transferred the bike, then
after that it is very important to transfer the insurance as well.
If you do not transfer the insurance, then
you will not get its claim. So,
today we will tell you how to transfer the
body slim body in ICICI company
in 5 minutes
online. So friends, first of all you have to
open your agent portal, login
in this portal.
After logging in, you will get the
endorsement, you have to
click on it and
enter it in it. We will tell you the portion on the fly number. After entering the
Bluetooth Bluetooth
Loot
Loot and
a military number, you will get it here. If there is any mistake in the
transfer, change of employee or RTO
location or change of NCVT option, then to
correct it, if you have to enter the
customer's address  To support the mistake, you will
get transfer of physical
and here you will get many more options, so you have to
click on transfer of tax and
after clicking on it you will get Prophet
click,
now you will get the name of the new customer, whether to enter the name of the new customer
in ghee transport or not,
date of birth,
date of loot, whatever is there, you limit it from here,
after increasing that date you have to enter your
carrier area pin code, after entering the pin code, you are
entering the full address which is above you
and for this festival you have to type,
after that you have to subscribe and your mobile number,
after that you have to enter half here, so
friends, as soon as you close your eyes in it,
you will get the option of plot allotment,
after uploading the how to, you should remember that after uploading,
split the documents with
folder in the research, these numbers have come,
after that you have to click on calculate,
you will have to do this at this much fee,
if you want to endorse this brother,
then winner  If you have
invested in the name of then they are soft,
you will have to pay in this, it is loading here,
you have to see the back of the neck or
loot,
so friends, I have waited a lot,
this server is down, I think I have been
waiting for the last 30 to 35 minutes, so the
click is not happening here, by the way,
its premium is ₹15, if you
invest in a private car or bike of third party, then you have to do it for ₹50,
after cutting it, you will get it, you will
get Play Services here,
after making the payment of Malik Beach,
you will immediately get Tulsi, if
you click on Tulsi, your policy will
also come on your email, that email ID is
in the job, it will be looted,
that person you will get the IDle option, you go
here and you will
get your policy, from here friends, if
you do not have such a portal, if you want to get
your investment done, then you
can also get the investment done from this email ID, I will click on this,
we will get you the investment done immediately, enter
in this email ID  Do
your new and C and if you do Tulsi
then we will give you 10 minutes for this,
you will get ₹50 plus
₹100, you will have to click on continue,
we will get you the endorsement done immediately within 10 to 15
minutes,
so thank you friends, to watch the video, do
like, share and subscribe,
if you liked the video then
tell me if you face any major problem
so that we can make a video of it and solve it,
thank you friends